<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>List of Secure Computation Papers</title>
    <link>https://guutboy.github.io</link>
    <description>A list of papers on IACR eprint on the topic of secure computation.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 15:36:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FPGA-based High-Performance Parallel Architecture for Homomorphic Computing on Encrypted Data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/160</link>
      <description>Sujoy Sinha Roy and Furkan Turan and Kimmo Jarvinen and Frederik Vercauteren and Ingrid Verbauwhede</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/160</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully homomorphic encryption modulo Fermat numbers</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/187</link>
      <description>Antoine Joux</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/187</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimized Homomorphic Encryption Solution for Secure Genome-Wide Association Studies</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/223</link>
      <description>Marcelo Blatt and Alexander Gusev and Yuriy Polyakov and Kurt Rohloff and Vinod Vaikuntanathan</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/223</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret-Sharing Schemes for General and Uniform Access Structures</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/231</link>
      <description>Benny Applebaum and Amos Beimel and Oriol Farràs and Oded Nir and Naty Peter</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/231</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressing Vector OLE</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/273</link>
      <description>Elette Boyle and Geoffroy Couteau and Niv Gilboa and Yuval Ishai</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/273</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path Oblivious Heap</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/274</link>
      <description>Elaine Shi</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/274</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPCircuits: Optimized Circuit Generation for Secure Multi-Party Computation</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/275</link>
      <description>M. Sadegh Riazi and Mojan Javaheripi and Siam U. Hussain and Farinaz Koushanfar</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/275</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Computation of the $k^\text{th}$-ranked Integer on Blockchains</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/276</link>
      <description>Erik-Oliver Blass and Florian Kerschbaum</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/276</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Algebraic Structures in the MPC Landscape</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/278</link>
      <description>Navneet Agarwal and Sanat Anand and Manoj Prabhakaran</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/278</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Some ROOM for the Zeros: Data Sparsity in Secure Distributed Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/281</link>
      <description>Phillipp Schoppmann and Adria Gascon and Mariana Raykova and Benny Pinkas</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/281</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-parallel Logistic Regression for GWAS on Encrypted Data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/294</link>
      <description>Miran Kim and Yongsoo Song and Baiyu Li and Daniele Micciancio</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/294</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Image Privacy and Usability with Thumbnail-Preserving Encryption</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/295</link>
      <description>Kimia Tajik and Akshith Gunasekaran and Rhea Dutta and Brandon Ellis and Rakesh B. Bobba and Mike Rosulek and Charles V. Wright and Wu-chi Feng</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/295</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Private Evaluation of a Decision Graph</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/325</link>
      <description>Hiroki Sudo and Koji Nuida and Kana Shimizu</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/325</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Key Homomophic Encryption from TFHE</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/116</link>
      <description>Hao Chen and Ilaria Chillotti and Yongsoo Song</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/116</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Compilation for Encrypted Computing</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/301</link>
      <description>Peter T. Breuer and Simon Pickin</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/301</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Private Comparison Queries over Encrypted Databases using Fully Homomorphic Encryption with Finite Fields</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/332</link>
      <description>Benjamin Hong Meng Tan and Hyung Tae Lee and Huaxiong Wang and Shu Qin Ren and Khin Mi Mi Aung</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/332</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practically Efficient Secure Distributed Exponentiation without Bit-Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/334</link>
      <description>Abdelrahaman Aly and Aysajan Abidin and Svetla Nikova </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/334</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbled Neural Networks are Practical</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/338</link>
      <description>Marshall Ball and Brent Carmer and Tal Malkin and Mike Rosulek and Nichole Shimanski</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/338</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Scalable Universal Circuits</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/348</link>
      <description>Masaud Y. Alhassan and Daniel Günther and Ágnes Kiss and Thomas Schneider</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/348</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nGraph-HE: A Graph Compiler for Deep Learning on Homomorphically Encrypted Data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/350</link>
      <description>Fabian Boemer and Yixing Lao and Rosario Cammarota and Casimir Wierzynski</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/350</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Privacy Preserving Scientific Operations</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/354</link>
      <description>Abdelrahaman Aly and Nigel P. Smart</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/354</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANNS: Scaling Up Secure Approximate k-Nearest Neighbors Search</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/359</link>
      <description>Hao Chen and Ilaria Chillotti and Yihe Dong and Oxana Poburinnaya and Ilya Razenshteyn and M. Sadegh Riazi</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/359</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lower Bounds for Oblivious Near-Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/377</link>
      <description>Kasper Green Larsen and Tal Malkin and Omri Weinstein and Kevin Yeo</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/377</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Single Shuffle Is Enough for Secure Card-Based Computation of Any Circuit</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/380</link>
      <description>Kazumasa Shinagawa and Koji Nuida</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/380</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Storage Access Privacy is Achievable with Small Overhead?</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/384</link>
      <description>Sarvar Patel and Giuseppe Persiano and Kevin Yeo</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/384</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Extension in Secret-Shared Form and Its Applications to Efficient Secure Computation</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/386</link>
      <description>Ryo Kikuchi and Nuttapong Attrapadung and Koki Hamada and Dai Ikarashi and Ai Ishida and Takahiro Matsuda and Yusuke Sakai and Jacob C. N. Schuldt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/386</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feistel Structures for MPC, and More </title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/397</link>
      <description>Martin R. Albrecht and Lorenzo Grassi and Le&amp;#769;o Perrin and Sebastian Ramacher and Christian Rechberger and Dragos Rotaru and Arnab Roy and Markus Schofnegger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/397</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Round Oblivious Transfer from CDH or LPN</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/414</link>
      <description>Nico Dottling and Sanjam Garg and Mohammad Hajiabadi and Daniel Masny and Daniel Wichs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/414</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical Methods for Comparison on Homomorphically Encrypted Numbers</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/417</link>
      <description>Jung Hee Cheon and Dongwoo Kim and Duhyeong Kim and Hun Hee Lee and Keewoo Lee</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/417</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algebraic Cryptanalysis of STARK-Friendly Designs: Application to MARVELlous and MiMC</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/419</link>
      <description>Martin R. Albrecht and Carlos Cid and Lorenzo Grassi and Dmitry Khovratovich and Reinhard Lüftenegger and Christian Rechberger and Markus Schofnegger</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/419</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homomorphic Training of 30,000 Logistic Regression Models</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/425</link>
      <description>Flavio Bergamaschi and Shai Halevi and Tzipora T. Halevi and Hamish Hunt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/425</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Symmetric Primitives for Advanced Cryptographic Protocols (A Marvellous Contribution)</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/426</link>
      <description>Abdelrahaman Aly and Tomer Ashur and Eli Ben-Sasson and Siemen Dhooghe and Alan Szepieniec</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/426</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Secure Integer Comparison via Homomorphic Encryption</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/427</link>
      <description>Florian Bourse and Olivier Sanders and Jacques Traoré</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/427</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRA: High Throughput 3PC over Rings with Application to Secure Prediction</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/429</link>
      <description>Harsh Chaudhari and Arpita Patra and Ajith Suresh</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/429</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient coding for secure computing with additively-homomorphic encrypted data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/437</link>
      <description>Thijs Veugen</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/437</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pseudorandom Correlation Generators: Silent OT Extension and More</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/448</link>
      <description>Elette Boyle and Geoffroy Couteau and Niv Gilboa and Yuval Ishai and Lisa Kohl and Peter Scholl</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/448</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Interactive MPC with Trusted Hardware Secure Against Residual Function Attacks</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/454</link>
      <description>Ryan Karl and Timothy Burchfield and Jonathan Takeshita and Taeho Jung</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/454</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Practical Clustering Analysis over Encrypted Data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/465</link>
      <description>Jung Hee Cheon and Duhyeong Kim and Jai Hyun Park</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/465</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving K-means Clustering with Multiple Data Owners</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/466</link>
      <description>Jung Hee Cheon and Jinhyuck Jeong and Dohyeong Ki and Jiseung Kim and Joohee Lee and Seok Won Lee</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/466</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Approach to the Secure Computation of the Moore-Penrose Pseudoinverse over the Rationals</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/470</link>
      <description>Niek J. Bouman and Niels de Vreede</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/470</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Filter Permutators: Combining Symmetric Encryption Design, Boolean Functions, Low Complexity Cryptography, and Homomorphic Encryption, for Private Delegation of Computations</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/483</link>
      <description>Pierrick Méaux and Claude Carlet and Anthony Journault and François-Xavier Standaert</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/483</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homomorphic noise growth in practice: comparing BGV and FV</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/493</link>
      <description>Anamaria Costache and Kim Laine and Rachel Player</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/493</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An HPR variant of the FV scheme: Computationally Cheaper, Asymptotically Faster</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/500</link>
      <description>Jean-Claude Bajard and Julien Eynard and Paulo Martins and Leonel Sousa and Vincent Zucca</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/500</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Party ECDSA from Hash Proof Systems and Efficient Instantiations</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/503</link>
      <description>Guilhem Castagnos and Dario Catalano and  Fabien Laguillaumie and Federico Savasta and Ida Tucker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/503</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Private Contact Discovery at Scale</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/517</link>
      <description>Daniel Kales and Christian Rechberger and Thomas Schneider and Matthias Senker and Christian Weinert</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/517</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Database Joins for Secret Shared Data</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/518</link>
      <description>Payman Mohassel and Peter Rindal and Mike Rosulek</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/518</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Homomorphic Encryption with k-bit Arithmetic Operations</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/521</link>
      <description>Benjamin M. Case and Shuhong Gao and Gengran Hu and Qiuxia Xu</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/521</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threshold ECDSA from ECDSA Assumptions: The Multiparty Case</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/523</link>
      <description>Jack Doerner and Yashvanth Kondi and Eysa Lee and abhi shelat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/523</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-Key Homomorphic Encryption with Packed Ciphertexts with Application to Oblivious Neural Network Inference</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/524</link>
      <description>Hao Chen and Wei Dai and Miran Kim and Yongsoo Song</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/524</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Bootstrapping of FHE over the integers with large prime message space</title>
      <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2019/561</link>
      <description>Zhizhu Lian and Yupu Hu and Hu Chen and  Baocang Wang</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2019/561</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
