<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>List of Secure Computation Papers</title><link>https://guutboy.github.io</link><description>A list of papers on IACR eprint on the topic of secure computation.</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 20:59:22 -0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Secure MPC: Laziness Leads to GOD</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/580</link><description>Saikrishna Badrinarayanan and Aayush Jain and Nathan Manohar and Amit Sahai</description></item><item><title>PIR-PSI: Scaling Private Contact Discovery</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/579</link><description>Daniel Demmler and Peter Rindal and Mike Rosulek and Ni Trieu</description></item><item><title>Optimizing Authenticated Garbling for Faster Secure Two-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/578</link><description>Jonathan Katz and Samuel Ranellucci and Mike Rosulek and Xiao Wang</description></item><item><title>Fast Distributed RSA Key Generation for Semi-Honest and Malicious Adversaries</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/577</link><description>Tore Kasper Frederiksen and Yehuda Lindell and Valery Osheter and Benny Pinkas</description></item><item><title>Round-Optimal Secure Multiparty Computation with Honest Majority</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/572</link><description>Prabhanjan Ananth and Arka Rai Choudhuri and Aarushi Goel and Abhishek Jain</description></item><item><title>Limits of Practical Sublinear Secure Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/571</link><description>Elette Boyle and Yuval Ishai and Antigoni Polychroniadou</description></item><item><title>Fast Large-Scale Honest-Majority MPC for Malicious Adversaries</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/570</link><description>Koji Chida and Daniel Genkin and Koki Hamada and Dai Ikarashi and Ryo Kikuchi and Yehuda Lindell and Ariel Nof</description></item><item><title>Homomorphic Encryption for Approximate Matrix Arithmetic</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/565</link><description>Jung Hee Cheon and Andrey Kim</description></item><item><title>Adaptive Garbled RAM from Laconic Oblivious Transfer</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/549</link><description>Sanjam Garg and Rafail Ostrovsky and Akshayaram Srinivasan</description></item><item><title>Must the Communication Graph of MPC Protocols be an Expander?</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/540</link><description>Elette Boyle and Ran Cohen and Deepesh Data and Pavel Hubacek</description></item><item><title>Ring packing and amortized FHEW bootstrapping</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/532</link><description>Daniele Micciancio and Jessica Sorrell</description></item><item><title>Location-Proof System based on Secure Multi-Party Computations</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/525</link><description>Aurélien Dupin and Jean-Marc Robert and Christophe Bidan</description></item><item><title>Highly Efficient and Reusable Private Function Evaluation with Linear Complexity</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/515</link><description>Osman Bicer and Muhammed Ali Bingol and Mehmet Sabir Kiraz</description></item><item><title>Secure Two-Party Computation over Unreliable Channels</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/506</link><description>Ran Gelles and Anat Paskin-Cherniavsky and Vassilis Zikas</description></item><item><title>Computer-aided proofs for multiparty computation with active security</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/502</link><description>Helene Haagh and Aleksandr Karbyshev and Sabine Oechsner and Bas Spitters and Pierre-Yves Strub</description></item><item><title>Secure Two-party Threshold ECDSA from ECDSA Assumptions</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/499</link><description>Jack Doerner and Yashvanth Kondi and Eysa Lee and abhi shelat</description></item><item><title>Efficient Delegated Private Set Intersection on Outsourced Private Datasets</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/496</link><description>Aydin Abadi and Sotirios Terzis and Roberto Metere and Changyu Dong</description></item><item><title>Approximating Private Set Union/Intersection Cardinality with Logarithmic Complexity</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/495</link><description>Changyu Dong and Grigorios Loukides</description></item><item><title>Pushing the Communication Barrier in Secure Computation using Lookup Tables</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/486</link><description>Ghada Dessouky and Farinaz Koushanfar and Ahmad-Reza Sadeghi and Thomas Schneider and Shaza Zeitouni and Michael Zohner</description></item><item><title>SPDZ2k: Efficient MPC mod 2^k for Dishonest Majority</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/482</link><description>Ronald Cramer and Ivan Damgård and Daniel Escudero and Peter Scholl and Chaoping Xing</description></item><item><title>On the Exact Round Complexity of Secure Three-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/481</link><description>Arpita Patra and Divya Ravi</description></item><item><title>Minimising Communication in Honest-Majority MPC by Batchwise Multiplication Verification</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/474</link><description>Peter Sebastian Nordholt and Meilof Veeningen</description></item><item><title>Secure Multi-Party Computation from Strongly Uniform Key Agreement</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/473</link><description>Daniele Friolo and Daniel Masny and Daniele Venturi</description></item><item><title>Efficient Range ORAM with $\mathbb{O}(\log^{2}{N})$ Locality</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/471</link><description>Anrin Chakraborti and Adam J. Aviv and Seung Geol Choi and Travis Mayberry and Daniel S. Roche and Radu Sion</description></item><item><title>The Usefulness of Sparsifiable Inputs: How to Avoid Subexponential iO</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/470</link><description>Thomas Agrikola and Geoffroy Couteau and Dennis Hofheinz</description></item><item><title>Error-Detecting in Monotone Span Programs with Application to Communication Efficient Multi-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/467</link><description>Nigel P. Smart and Tim Wood</description></item><item><title>A Note on the Communication Complexity of Multiparty Computation in the Correlated Randomness Model</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/465</link><description>Geoffroy Couteau</description></item><item><title>Logistic regression over encrypted data from fully homomorphic encryption</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/462</link><description>Hao Chen and Ran Gilad-Bachrach and Kyoohyung Han and Zhicong Huang and Amir Jalali and Kim Laine and Kristin Lauter</description></item><item><title>From FE Combiners to Secure MPC and Back</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/457</link><description>Prabhanjan Ananth and Saikrishna Badrinarayanan and Aayush Jain and Nathan Manohar and Amit Sahai</description></item><item><title>From Keys to Databases -- Real-World Applications of Secure Multi-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/450</link><description>David W. Archer and Dan Bogdanov and Y. Lindell and Liina Kamm and Kurt Nielsen and Jakob Illeborg Pagter and Nigel P. Smart and Rebecca N. Wright</description></item><item><title>Founding Cryptography on Smooth Projective Hashing</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/444</link><description>Bing Zeng</description></item><item><title>Quantum Multi-Key Homomorphic Encryption for Polynomial-Sized Circuits</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/443</link><description>Rishab Goyal</description></item><item><title>SecureNN: Efficient and Private Neural Network Training</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/442</link><description>Sameer Wagh and Divya Gupta and Nishanth Chandran</description></item><item><title>Amortized Complexity of Information-Theoretically Secure MPC Revisited</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/429</link><description>Ignacio Cascudo and Ronald Cramer and Chaoping Xing and Chen Yuan</description></item><item><title>Yes, There is an Oblivious RAM Lower Bound!</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/423</link><description>Kasper Green Larsen and Jesper Buus Nielsen</description></item><item><title>TFHE: Fast Fully Homomorphic Encryption over the Torus</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/421</link><description>Ilaria Chillotti and Nicolas Gama and Mariya Georgieva and Malika Izabachène</description></item><item><title>Homomorphic Secret Sharing: Optimizations and Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/419</link><description>Elette Boyle and Geoffroy Couteau and Niv Gilboa and Yuval Ishai and Michele Orrù</description></item><item><title>Unsupervised Machine Learning on Encrypted Data</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/411</link><description>Angela Jäschke and Frederik Armknecht</description></item><item><title>Laconic Function Evaluation and Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/409</link><description>Willy Quach and Hoeteck Wee and Daniel Wichs</description></item><item><title>Enforcing ideal-world leakage bounds in real-world secret sharing MPC frameworks</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/404</link><description>José Bacelar Almeida and Manuel Barbosa and Gilles Barthe and Hugo Pacheco and Vitor Pereira and Bernardo Portela</description></item><item><title>ABY3: A Mixed Protocol Framework for Machine Learning</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/403</link><description>Payman Mohassel and Peter Rindal</description></item><item><title>Embedding Multiplications at a Linear Rate and its Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/395</link><description>Alexander R. Block and Hemanta K. Maji and Hai H. Nguyen</description></item><item><title>Efficient Bit-Decomposition and Modulus-Conversion Protocols with an Honest Majority</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/387</link><description>Ryo Kikuchi and Dai Ikarashi and Takahiro Matsuda and Koki Hamada and Koji Chida</description></item><item><title>PanORAMa: Oblivious RAM with Logarithmic Overhead</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/373</link><description>Sarvar Patel and Giuseppe Persiano and Mariana Raykova and Kevin Yeo</description></item><item><title>Secure Computation using Leaky Correlations (Asymptotically Optimal Constructions)</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/372</link><description>Alexander R. Block and Divya Gupta and Hemanta K. Maji and Hai H. Nguyen</description></item><item><title>Perfectly Secure Oblivious Parallel RAM</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/364</link><description>T-H. Hubert Chan and Kartik Nayak and Elaine Shi</description></item><item><title>Private Anonymous Data Access</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/363</link><description>Ariel Hamlin and Rafail Ostrovsky and Mor Weiss and Daniel Wichs</description></item><item><title>Privacy-Preserving Multibiometric Authentication in Cloud with Untrusted Database Providers</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/359</link><description>Christina-Angeliki Toli and Abdelrahaman Aly and Bart Preneel</description></item><item><title>3PC ORAM with Low Latency, Low Bandwidth, and Fast Batch Retrieval</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/347</link><description>Stanislaw Jarecki and Boyang Wei</description></item><item><title>Nothing Refreshes Like a RePSI: Reactive Private Set Intersection</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/344</link><description>Andrea Cerulli and Emiliano De Cristofaro and Claudio Soriente</description></item></channel></rss>