<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>List of Secure Computation Papers</title><link>https://guutboy.github.io</link><description>A list of papers on IACR eprint on the topic of secure computation.</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 08:58:40 -0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Error-Detecting in Monotone Span Programs with Application to Communication Efficient Multi-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/467</link><description>Nigel P. Smart and Tim Wood</description></item><item><title>A Note on the Communication Complexity of Multiparty Computation in the Correlated Randomness Model</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/465</link><description>Geoffroy Couteau</description></item><item><title>Logistic regression over encrypted data from fully homomorphic encryption</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/462</link><description>Hao Chen and Ran Gilad-Bachrach and Kyoohyung Han and Zhicong Huang and Amir Jalali and Kim Laine and Kristin Lauter</description></item><item><title>From FE Combiners to Secure MPC and Back</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/457</link><description>Prabhanjan Ananth and Saikrishna Badrinarayanan and Aayush Jain and Nathan Manohar and Amit Sahai</description></item><item><title>From Keys to Databases -- Real-World Applications of Secure Multi-Party Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/450</link><description>David W. Archer and Dan Bogdanov and Y. Lindell and Liina Kamm and Kurt Nielsen and Jakob Illeborg Pagter and Nigel P. Smart and Rebecca N. Wright</description></item><item><title>Founding Cryptography on Smooth Projective Hashing</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/444</link><description>Bing Zeng</description></item><item><title>Quantum Multi-Key Homomorphic Encryption for Polynomial-Sized Circuits</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/443</link><description>Rishab Goyal</description></item><item><title>SecureNN: Efficient and Private Neural Network Training</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/442</link><description>Sameer Wagh and Divya Gupta and Nishanth Chandran</description></item><item><title>Amortized Complexity of Information-Theoretically Secure MPC Revisited</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/429</link><description>Ignacio Cascudo and Ronald Cramer and Chaoping Xing and Chen Yuan</description></item><item><title>Yes, There is an Oblivious RAM Lower Bound!</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/423</link><description>Kasper Green Larsen and Jesper Buus Nielsen</description></item><item><title>TFHE: Fast Fully Homomorphic Encryption over the Torus</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/421</link><description>Ilaria Chillotti and Nicolas Gama and Mariya Georgieva and Malika Izabachène</description></item><item><title>Homomorphic Secret Sharing: Optimizations and Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/419</link><description>Elette Boyle and Geoffroy Couteau and Niv Gilboa and Yuval Ishai and Michele Orrù</description></item><item><title>Unsupervised Machine Learning on Encrypted Data</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/411</link><description>Angela Jäschke and Frederik Armknecht</description></item><item><title>Laconic Function Evaluation and Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/409</link><description>Willy Quach and Hoeteck Wee and Daniel Wichs</description></item><item><title>Enforcing ideal-world leakage bounds in real-world secret sharing MPC frameworks</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/404</link><description>José Bacelar Almeida and Manuel Barbosa and Gilles Barthe and Hugo Pacheco and Vitor Pereira and Bernardo Portela</description></item><item><title>ABY3: A Mixed Protocol Framework for Machine Learning</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/403</link><description>Payman Mohassel and Peter Rindal</description></item><item><title>Embedding Multiplications at a Linear Rate and its Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/395</link><description>Alexander R. Block and Hemanta K. Maji and Hai H. Nguyen</description></item><item><title>Efficient Bit-Decomposition and Modulus-Conversion Protocols with an Honest Majority</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/387</link><description>Ryo Kikuchi and Dai Ikarashi and Takahiro Matsuda and Koki Hamada and Koji Chida</description></item><item><title>PanORAMa: Oblivious RAM with Logarithmic Overhead</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/373</link><description>Sarvar Patel and Giuseppe Persiano and Mariana Raykova and Kevin Yeo</description></item><item><title>Secure Computation using Leaky Correlations (Asymptotically Optimal Constructions)</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/372</link><description>Alexander R. Block and Divya Gupta and Hemanta K. Maji and Hai H. Nguyen</description></item><item><title>Perfectly Secure Oblivious Parallel RAM</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/364</link><description>T-H. Hubert Chan and Kartik Nayak and Elaine Shi</description></item><item><title>Private Anonymous Data Access</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/363</link><description>Ariel Hamlin and Rafail Ostrovsky and Mor Weiss and Daniel Wichs</description></item><item><title>Privacy-Preserving Multibiometric Authentication in Cloud with Untrusted Database Providers</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/359</link><description>Christina-Angeliki Toli and Abdelrahaman Aly and Bart Preneel</description></item><item><title>3PC ORAM with Low Latency, Low Bandwidth, and Fast Batch Retrieval</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/347</link><description>Stanislaw Jarecki and Boyang Wei</description></item><item><title>Nothing Refreshes Like a RePSI: Reactive Private Set Intersection</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/344</link><description>Andrea Cerulli and Emiliano De Cristofaro and Claudio Soriente</description></item><item><title>Quantum FHE (Almost) As Secure as Classical</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/338</link><description>Zvika Brakerski</description></item><item><title>PPAD: Privacy Preserving Group-Based ADvertising in Online Social Networks</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/323</link><description>Sanaz Taheri Boshrooyeh and Alptekin Küpçü and Öznur Özkasap</description></item><item><title>Secure top most significant genome variants search: iDASH 2017 competition</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/314</link><description>Sergiu Carpov and Thibaud Tortech</description></item><item><title>On Perfectly Secure 2PC in the OT-hybrid model</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/308</link><description>Anat Paskin-Cherniavsky</description></item><item><title>Outsourcing Modular Exponentiation in Cryptographic Web Applications</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/300</link><description>Pascal Mainini and Rolf Haenni</description></item><item><title>Fine-Grained Secure Computation</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/297</link><description>Matteo Campanelli and Rosario Gennaro</description></item><item><title>Private Nearest Neighbors Classification in Federated Databases</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/289</link><description>Phillipp Schoppmann and Adrià Gascón and Borja Balle</description></item><item><title>Homomorphic Rank Sort Using Surrogate Polynomials</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/283</link><description>Gizem S. Çetin and Berk Sunar</description></item><item><title>Oblivious RAM with Small Storage Overhead</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/268</link><description>Michael Raskin and Mark Simkin</description></item><item><title>Logistic Regression Model Training based on the Approximate Homomorphic Encryption</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/254</link><description>Andrey Kim and Yongsoo Song and Miran Kim and Keewoo Lee and Jung Hee Cheon</description></item><item><title>Making Public Key Functional Encryption Function Private, Distributively</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/250</link><description>Xiong Fan and Qiang Tang</description></item><item><title>Faster Homomorphic Linear Transformations in HElib</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/244</link><description>Shai Halevi and Victor Shoup</description></item><item><title>Private Set Intersection with Linear Communication from General Assumptions</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/238</link><description>Brett Hemenway Falk and Daniel Noble and Rafail Ostrovsky</description></item><item><title>P2KMV: A Privacy-preserving Counting Sketch for Efficient and Accurate Set Intersection Cardinality Estimations</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/234</link><description>Hagen Sparka and Florian Tschorsch and Björn Scheuermann</description></item><item><title>Privacy-Preserving Logistic Regression Training</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/233</link><description>Charlotte Bonte and Frederik Vercauteren</description></item><item><title>Improved fully homomorphic public-key encryption with small ciphertext size</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/232</link><description>Masahiro Yagisawa</description></item><item><title>Can We Overcome the $n \log n$ Barrier for Oblivious Sorting?</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/227</link><description>Wei-Kai Lin and Elaine Shi and Tiancheng Xie</description></item><item><title>PRO-ORAM: Constant Latency Read-Only Oblivious RAM</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/220</link><description>Shruti Tople and Yaoqi Jia and Prateek Saxena</description></item><item><title>Secure Computation with Low Communication from Cross-checking</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/216</link><description>S. Dov Gordon and Samuel Ranellucci and Xiao Wang</description></item><item><title>Efficient MPC from Syndrome Decoding (or: Honey, I Shrunk the Keys)</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/208</link><description>Carmit Hazay and Emmanuela Orsini and Peter Scholl and Eduardo Soria-Vazquez</description></item><item><title>Reading in the Dark: Classifying Encrypted Digits with Functional Encryption</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/206</link><description>Edouard Dufour Sans and Romain Gay and David Pointcheval</description></item><item><title>Doing Real Work with FHE: The Case of Logistic Regression</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/202</link><description>Jack L.H. Crawford and Craig Gentry and Shai Halevi and Daniel Platt and Victor Shoup</description></item><item><title>Efficient Parallel Binary Operations on Homomorphic Encrypted Real Numbers</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/201</link><description>Jim Basilakis and Bahman Javadi</description></item><item><title>Can you find the one for me? Privacy-Preserving Matchmaking via Threshold PSI</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/184</link><description>Yongjun Zhao and Sherman S. M. Chow</description></item><item><title>Rasta: A cipher with low ANDdepth and few ANDs per bit</title><link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2018/181</link><description>Christoph Dobraunig and Maria Eichlseder and Lorenzo Grassi and Virginie Lallemand and Gregor Leander and Eik List and Florian Mendel and Christian Rechberger</description></item></channel></rss>